Zack, Arnold M. Additional Arbitration Files 6250
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files
1955-2012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold M.
6250
9.5 cubic feet
9.5 linear ft.
Papers.
6250376
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, March 21, 2008
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 27, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5281: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5512: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files 5551: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5727: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5786: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5825: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5861: Arnold M. Zack Additional Arbitration Files 5913: Arnold Zack Additional Aarbitration Files 5950: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 5979: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6049: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases 6066: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6104: Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Files 6141: Arnold Zack Arbitration Files
Arbitration, Industrial; Zack, Arnold; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; National Treasury Employees Union; Office and Professional Employees International Union; United Food and Commercial Workers International Union
6250376
- AirTran Airways / National Pilots Association (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AT&T / CWA (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bristol County Sheriff's Office / MCOFU (Folder 1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Bristol County Sheriff's Office / MCOFU (Folder 2 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Bristol County Sheriff's Office / MCOFU (Folder 3 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bristol County Sheriff's Office / MCOFU (Folder 4 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Connecticut Light and Power / IBEW (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Connecticut Transit Authority / Amalgamated Transit Union (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Express Jet (Continental) Air / Teamsters (Box 1, Folder 9)
- First Student / CSEA / SEIU (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Haverhill Paperboard / USWIU (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Huhtamaki / USWIU (Box 1, Folder 12)
- IRS / NTEU (Part 1 of 4) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- IRS / NTEU (Part 2 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- IRS / NTEU (Part 3 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- IRS / NTEU (Part 4 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- IRS / NTEU (Part 4 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- MA Sportservice / UFCW (Part 1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- MA Sportservice / UFCW (Part 2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- MA Sportservice / UFCW (Part 3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 7)
- New Hampshire State Employees Factfinding Session (Box 2, Folder 8)
- RISD / RISD Public Safety Officers' Association (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 1 of 17) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 2 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 3 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 4 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 5 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 6 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 7 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 8 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 9 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 10 of 17) (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Shaws Supermarkets: Joint Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Shaws Supermarkets: Company Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Shaws Supermarkets: Union Exhibits (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 11 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 12 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 13 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 14 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 15 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 16 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Shaws Supermarkets / UFCW (Part 17 of 17) (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Shaws Supermarkets: Wakefield, MA, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  Scope and Contents
  May 8th. Wakefield, MA
- Shaws SupermarketsL: Braintree, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  Jan. 10th
- Trial Court of MA / OPEIU (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Umass Medical Center / UFCW (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Verizon / IBEW (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Worcester County Sheriff's Office / MCOFU (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Wyman Gordan / USA (Box 4, Folder 14)
- New Bedford Police Int. Arb. JMLC-04-24P, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Warwick Sch Cmte/ Teachers Union #711-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  9/11/07;1 of 3; 1 pamphlet
- Warwick Sch Cmte/ Teachers Union #711-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  9/11/07; 2 of 3
- Warwick Sch Cmte/ Teachers Union #711-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  9/11/07; 3 of 3
- Alliance Imaging/ Teamsters, re: D. Hines 391, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  9/10/07-10/10/07; 1 of 2
- Alliance Imaging/ Teamsters, re: D. Hines 391, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  9/10/07-10/10/07; 2 of 2; photos
- NSTAR and UWUA 369, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  11/1/07; Griev. #7160; 1 pamphlet
- Entergy/ UWUA 369, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  11/20/07; 1 of 2
- Entergy/ UWUA 369, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  11/20/07; 2 of 2
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 1 of 7; 2 pamphlets
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 2 of 7
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 3 of 7
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 4 of 7
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 5 of 7
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 6 of 7
- Stop and Shop/ UFCW 1445 #716-07, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  8/8/07-12/14/07; 7 of 7
- Shaws/ UFCW #2074-04, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  1 of 2
- Shaws/ UFCW #2074-04, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  2 of 2
- Shaws/ UFCW 1273-02, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  1/4/08;1 of 5
- Shaws/ UFCW 1273-02, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  1/4/08; 2 of 5
- Shaws/UFCW 1273-02, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  1/4/08; 3 of 5
- Shaws/ UFCW1273-02, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  1/4/08; 4 of 5
- Shaws/ UFCW 1273-02, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  1/4/08; 5 of 5; 2 pamphlets
- Sinclair Broadcast/ IBEW 1837 #FMCS07-04577, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  1/29/2008
- Warwick Public Sch./WISE 1104-07, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  2/12/08
- Stafford City DOC/ Riverside Rest Home/SEIU 1984, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  3/21/08
- FDIC/ NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 1 of 6
- FDIC/ NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 2 of 6
- FDIC/ NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 3 of 6
- FDIC/ NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 4 of 6
- FDIC/ NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 5 of 6
- FDIC/NTEU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  4/9 and 4/10/08; 6 of 6
- Tiverton School Committee/ NEA, RI #94-08, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  6/10/08
- IRS/ NTEU Chapter 99, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  6/12/08; 1 of 2
- IRS/ NTEU Chapter 99, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  6/12/08; 2 of 2
- American Medical Response/ IAEP 329-08, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  11/3/08; 1 of 2; contains 1 cd
- American Medical Response/ IAEP 329-08, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  11/3/08; 2 of 2
- UMASS Memorial/ MNA 1563-08, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  12/16/08
- Bristol City/ MCOFU, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  Melo case clarification request
- Rensselaer Cty/ Sheriff's Emp #A2008-316, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  2/24/2009 and 3/30/2009; 1 of 2; Albany, NY; contains 2 cds
- Rensselaer Cty/ Sheriff's Emp #A2008-316, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  2/24/09 and 3/30/09; 2 of 2; Albany, NY
- Comm of MA/ SEIU 508, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  6/4/09; Arb. #6861
- Hollywood Greyhound Track/ Unite 639-08, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  6/17/2009
- Faulkner Hosp/MNA 276-08, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  9/21/09
- Bedford, NH/ Firefighters NHPELRBGO -00901, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  11/8/09
- Springfield School Committee/Springfield Special Education Association 1038-09, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  11/16/09 and 11/18/09
- NEA New Hampshire/New Hampshire Education Staff Association, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  1 of 4
- NEA New Hampshire/New Hampshire Education Staff Association, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  2 of 4
- NEA New Hampshire/New Hampshire Education Staff Association, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  3 of 4
- NEA New Hampshire/New Hampshire Education Staff Association, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  4 of 4
- Proctor and Gamble, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  1/29/10, 1 of 2, Avenel, NJ
- Proctor and Gamble, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  1/29/10, 2 of 2, Avenel, NJ
- Walnut Street Center/SEIU 509 #778-09, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  12/3/09 and 2/9/10; 1 of 2; AAA, Boston
- Walnut Street Center/ SEIU 509 #778-09, 2009-2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  12/3/09 and 2/9/10; 2 of 2; AAA, Boston
- NHESO/NEA New Hampshire 1490-09, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  3/12/10; 1 of 2; Concord, NH
- NHESO/ NEA New Hampshire 1490-09, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  3/12/10; 2 of 2; Concord, NH
- WFSB-TV/NABET 269-09, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  4/1/10; E. Hartford, CT
- AT&T/ CWA D1-02-2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  6/17/2010; 1 of 3
- AT&T/ CWA D1-02-2010 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  6/17/2010; 2 of 3
- AT&T/CWA D1-02-2010 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  6/17/2010; 3 of 3
- AT&T/CWA, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  March 16, 2011
- AT&T Midwest/CWA Local 4123, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  February 23, 2011
- Bristol City Sheriff/MCOFU, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  January 21, 2011
- Bristol City Sheriff Office/MCOFU, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  November 10, 2010
- Capital Waste/Teamsters Local 25: no.865-11, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  October 12, 2011
- Customs/NTEU: Waiters, JFK [folder 1 0f 2], 2012 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  November 29, 2012
- Customs/NTEU: Waiters, JFK [folder 2 of 2], 2012 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Customs/NTEU: Brooks, Burlington VT, 2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  October 25, 2012
- Customs/NTEU: Bid Rotation, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  April 6, 2011
- Customs/NTEU: Bid Rotation and Placement, Portland ME [folder 1 of 3], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Customs/NTEU: Bid Rotation and Placement, Portland ME [folder 2 of 3], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Customs/NTEU: Bid Rotation and Placement, Portland ME [folder 3 of 3], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Falmouth/Police: no.1725-09, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  March 22, 2011
- Hampton City Sheriff/Employees, Ludlow MA, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  March 8, 1011
- Management and Training Corporation/IUD/CWA: no.1605-10, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  March 28, 2011
- Manchester NH/Police Patrolmen: no.G0103-3 [folder 1 of 4], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  November 10, 2011
- Manchester NH/Police Patrolmen: no.G0103-3 [folder 2 of 4], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Manchester NH/Police Patrolmen: no.G0103-3 [folder 3 of 4], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Manchester NH/Police Patrolmen: no.G0103-3 [folder 4 of 4], 2011 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- UGL UNICCO/SEIU: no.1870-10, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  February 24, 2011
- US Customs/NTEU Chapter 154 [folder 1 of 2], 2011 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  September 26, 2011
- US Customs/NTEU Chapter 154 [folder 2 of 2], 2011 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Wakefield Gas and Electric/Employee Association: no.1344-12, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  November 13, 2012
- Warwick Public Schools/WISE: no.1867-09, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  June 3, 2010
- Warwick Public Schools/Warwick Teachers Union: no.564-10 [folder 1 of 5], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Warwick Public Schools/Warwick Teachers Union: no.564-10 [folder 2 of 5], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Warwick Public Schools/Warwick Teachers Union: no.564-10 [folder 3 of 5], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Warwick Public Schools/Warwick Teachers Union: no.564-10 [folder 4 of 5], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Warwick Public Schools/Warwick Teachers Union: no.564-10 [folder 5 of 5], 2010 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 1 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 2 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 3 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 4 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 5 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 6 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 7 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 8 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 9 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 10 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 11 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 12 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 13 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 14 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 15 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Greater Lowell School Committee/Teachers: no.490-11 [folder 16 of 16], 2010-2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- The East European Student and Youth Service, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Michael Zack: Russia, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)